friendimobile.om 2016-11-24

# Privacy policy - FRiENDi mobile

MOBILE PRIVACY POLICY FRiENDi mobile understands that privacy is important to you. We are committed to complying with international best practice privacy principles. We will treat your personal information as confidential in accordance with the laws of Oman concerning privacy rights.

**What personal information does FRiENDi mobile collect?**  
We may collect personal information from you when you subscribe to our mobile telephony services or use our websites, for example to book numbers. The personal information we will collect from you will usually include your name, national ID number, nationality and address. However, we do not collect personal information that we do not need.

**How does FRiENDi mobile use personal information?**  
We need to collect personal information so that we can provide our products and services to you. We also collect personal information in order to:

  * Comply with our legal and regulatory requirements of national security agencies and other official governmental bodies
  * Communicate any changes to your services and advise you of our new products and services

If (at any time) you wish to contact us about communications you receive from us, our contact details are set out on our web site.

FRiENDi mobile's policy is only to use personal information collected from business contacts for the business purpose for which it was collected.

 **Will your personal information be given to anyone else?**  
FRiENDi mobile does not sell, rent, trade or disclose personal information about you to or with third parties. FRiENDi mobile will only disclose personal information if this is required by or permitted by law. 

**How secure is your personal information?**  
FRiENDi mobile takes reasonable steps to ensure the security of your personal information. Our premises are in a secure building with access restricted to passcard holders. Our IT systems are password protected and we conduct regular audit and data integrity checks. We frequently update our anti-virus software in order to protect our systems (and the data contained in those systems) from computer viruses. In addition, all FRiENDi mobile employees are required, as a condition of employment, to treat personal information held by FRiENDi mobile as confidential. 

**Can I correct any inaccurate personal information?**  
You may ask us to update or correct your personal information when it is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date by using our contact details set out on our web site. In accessing your account, and/or requesting changes to any account details, your existing passwords and account details will be used to verify your identity. 

**What about information collected on FRiENDi mobile's web site?**  
As noted above, sometimes we may collect personal information through our website (if, for example, you book your number on-line). This will be limited to your name, phone number and your national ID number and your nationality.

Like most website providers, we generate statistics about how many people visit our site and what they look at. We use web logs and cookies to do this. This information is used internally only to help us to improve our service to you or to identify and correct problems with our servers and for systems administration. This enables us to keep our site relevant and useful. However, this information will not identify you.

Our website may contain links to other websites, for your convenience and information. When you access a website other than [www.friendimobile.om](http://www.friendimobile.om/ "Friendi Mobile") , please understand that FRiENDi mobile is not responsible for the privacy practices of that site. We suggest that you review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
